Guide to the Philosophy of Science Association Records, 1959-2005 ASP.1992.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Journal Management, 1970-1996; V.
  - Editor Selection Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Editorial Board, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Editorial Board Ballots, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Editorial Board Election Ballots, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Editorial Selection Committee, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Inventory, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Inventory, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Inventory, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Journal Dispute, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Journal Dispute, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Journal Editor Information, no date (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Journal Editor Search, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Journal Editor Search, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Manuscripts Received, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Suggestions- Journal Operation 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Governing Board, 1970-1996; VI.
  Governing Board series documents the activities and proceedings of the PSA Governing Board between 1970-1996. Files include minutes, correspondence and meeting documentation created by the Governing Board as well as documentation of the development of the Association's constitution and bylaws.
  - Constitution, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Constitution Revisions, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Constitution Revisions, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Constitution Revisions, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Funding Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Governing Board, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Governing Board, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Governing Board, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Governing Board, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Governing Board, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Governing Board, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Governing Board, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Governing Board, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Governing Board, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Governing Board, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Governing Board, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Governing Board, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Governing Board, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Governing Board, 1990-1996 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Governing Board Correspondence, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Governing Board Meetings, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Governing Board Minutes, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Governing Board Questionnaires, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Proceedings and Newsletter, Editor Search, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Proceedings- General, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Proceedings Publication, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - By-Laws Drafts, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Travel Grants, 1994-1995; VII.
  Travel Grants series contains documentation of Travel Grants awarded to membership for the Biennial Meetings of the Philosophy of Science Association between 1994-1995.
  - PSA Travel Grant (Biennial Meeting), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Travel Grants, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Travel Grants, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Correspondence, 1974-1997; VIII.
  Correspondence series contains communications created by members of the Philosophy of Science Association regarding administrative issues between 1974-1997. The bulk of the series is comprised of printed documentation of the communications created by the PSA's e-mail server.
  - Suppes Quantum Mechanics Book, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - PSA E-mails, May 1995-September 1995 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - PSA E-mails, October 1995-November 1995 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - PSA E-mails, December 1995-February 1996 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - PSA E-mails, February 1996-May 1996 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - PSA E-mails, May 1996-July 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - PSA E-mails, August 1996-October 1996 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - PSA E-mails, October 1996-January 1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - PSA E-mails, January 1997-April 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Report on PSA Research Problems in the Philosophy of Science Project by Henry Kyburg and Peter Asquith, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Report on PSA Research Problems in the Philosophy of Science Project by Henry Kyburg and Peter Asquith, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Yugoslav Philosophers, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Election Files, 1972-1995; IX.
  Election Files series contains documentation of elections held for the PSA Governing Board between 1972-1995. The series also contains meeting notes and correspondence created by the Nominating Committee in relation to the planning and conducting of board elections.
  - Election, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Election, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Election, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Election, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Election, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Election, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Election, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Election, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Election, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Election, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Election, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Election, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Election, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Election, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Election, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Election, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Election, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Election, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Election, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Election, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Election, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Election, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Election, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Nominating Committee, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Nominating Committee, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Nominating Committee, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Nominating Committee, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Nominating Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Nominating Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Nominating Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Nominating Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Nominating Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Nominating Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Nominating Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Joint Conferences, 1977-1982; X.
  Joint Conferences series contains documentation of conferences held in conjunction with other professional scientific and philosophical organizations and the PSA between 1977-1982. Conferences include the PSA Critical Research Problems Conference, Science and Technology Studies and Ethics and Values in Science and Technology held in conjunction with the National Science Foundation.
  - PSA Critical Research Problems Conference Tentative Program, no date (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Joint Meeting: Science and Technology Studies (Toronto), 1980 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Ethics and Values in Science and Technology Program of National Science Foundation, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Ethics and Values in Science and Technology Program of National Science Foundation, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Science and Technology Studies Conference Program, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Science and Technology Studies Conference Program, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Financial Records, 1974-1996; XI.
  Financial Records series contains financial documentation kept in relation to the administration of the Philosophy of Science Association between 1974-1996. Files include journal publishing finances, tax information and non-profit status reports.
  - Data Products Corporation, 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., 1994 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Edwards Brothers, Inc., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Legal Expenses, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Michigan Non-Profit Corporation Report, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Michigan Non-Profit Corporation Report, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Michigan Non-Profit Corporation Report, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Michigan Non-Profit Corporation Report, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Michigan Non-Profit Corporation Report, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Michigan Non-Profit Corporation Report, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Michigan Non-Profit Corporation Report, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Purchasing, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Purchasing: NEBS Computer Forms, 1991-1996 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Membership Information, 1973-1996; XII.
  Directories series contains membership directories and PSA Governing Board listings between 1987-1996.
  - Philosophy of Science Association Directory, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Philosophy of Science Association Directory, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Philosophy of Science Association Directory, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Philosophy of Science Association Directory, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Philosophy of Science Association Directory, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Philosophy of Science Association Directory, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Philosophy of Science Association Directory, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Philosophy of Science Association Directory, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Philosophy of Science Association Directory, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Membership Advertising, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Membership Questionnaire, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - PSA Member Suggestions from 1973 Ballot (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Membership Questionnaire Proposal, no date (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Newsletters, 1976-1990; XIII.
  Newsletters series contains issues of the official PSA membership newsletter distributed between 1976 and 1990. Newsletters often contained reporting on PSA business and newsworthy items regarding individual PSA members, as well as information regarding upcoming biennial meetings.
  - Newsletter Volume 6, No. 2-3, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Newsletter Volume 7, No. 1-3, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter Volume 7, No. 1-3, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter Volume 8, No. 1-4, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Newsletter Volume 8, No. 1-4, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter Volume 9, No. 1-3, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter Volume 9, No. 1-3, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Newsletter Volume 10, No. 1-2, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter Volume 10, No. 3-4, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Newsletter Volume 10, No. 4, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter Volume 11, No.1-4, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter Volume 11, No.1-4, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter Volume 12, No.1-4, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter Volume 13, No. 1-4, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter Volume 14, No.2, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Newsletter Volume 14, No.2-4, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter Volume 15, No.1-4, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter Volume 16, No.1-4, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Newsletter Volume 17, No.1-4, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Newsletter Volume 18, No.1-4, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Newsletter Volume 19, No.1-4, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter General Info, 1978-1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter Mailing List, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Journal Issues, 1959-1960; XIV.
  Series XV. Journal Issues contains published copies of the PSA Journal, ranging from 1959-1961.
  - PSA Journal Vol. 26 No. 1, January, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - PSA Journal Vol 26. No. 2, April, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - PSA Journal Vol. 26 No. 3, July, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - PSA Journal Vol. 26 No. 4, October, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - PSA Journal Vol. 27 No. 1, January, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - PSA Journal Vol. 27 No. 2, April, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - PSA Journal Vol. 27 No. 3, July, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - PSA Journal Vol. 27 No. 4, October, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - PSA Journal Vol. 28 No. 1, January, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Biennial Meeting Papers and Symposia Submissions, 1996-2002; XV.
  Series XV. Biennial Meetings Papers and Symposia Submissions contains contributed papers and symposia which were presented at the Philosophy of Science Association's Biennial Meeting. Papers were also published in the Philosophy of Science Journal following their presentation at the meeting. Submission files for contributed papers and symposia are filed similarly to Philosophy of Science Journal files and are labeled by last name and title. Each file contains an acceptance or rejection letter as well as correspondence, edited drafts and proofs.
  Access Restrictions
  Access to Subseries 7. Rejected Biennial Meeting Papers and Symposia Submissions are restricted for 75 years from date of submission.
  - PSA 1996 (Cleveland, Ohio) Accepted Contributed Papers, 1.
    Subseries 1. PSA 1996 (Cleveland, Ohio) Accepted Contributed Papers contains submission files for the Philosophy of Science biennial meeting held in Cleveland Ohio in 1996.
    - Allchin, Douglas, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Ariew, Andre, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Bandyopadhyay, Prasanta, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Barret, Jeffrey A., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Belot, Gordon, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Bradie, Michael, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Chinn, Clark A., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Clark, Austen, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Clifton, Rob, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Cooper, Greg, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Cushing, James, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Dedrick, Don, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - DeVito, Scott, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Dickson, Michael, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Douvne, Igor, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Gorham, Geoffrey, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Griffiths, Paul E., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Guarini, Marcello, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Hall, Richard J., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Harper, William, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Hemmo, Meir, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Hugget, Nick, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Andre Kukla, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Liu, Chuang, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Melnyk, Andrew, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Mikkelson, Gregory M., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Millstein, Roberta L., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Parascandola, Mark, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Psillos, Stathis, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Ruetsche, Laura, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Rynasiewicz, Robert, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Sargent, Pauline, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Schmaus, Warren, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Schwitzgebel, Eric, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Seidenfeld, Teddy, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Shaffer, Nancy E., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Siegel, Harvey, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Staley, Kent, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Vance, Russell E., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Vineberg, Susan, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Weinstein, Steve, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - PSA 1996 (Cleveland, Ohio) Accepted Symposia, 2.
    Subseries 2. PSA 1996 (Cleveland, OH) Accepted Symposia contains submission files for symposia papers to be presented at the Philosophy of Science biennial meeting held in Cleveland, Ohio in 1996.
    - Beatty, John, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Burian, Richard, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Burkholder, Leslie, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Callender, Craig, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Hausman, Daniel, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Hentschel, Klaus, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Humphreys, Paul, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Longino, Helen E., 1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Mayo, Deborah G., 1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Mirowski, Philip E., 1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Morgan, Mary S., 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Preston, John, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Stufflebeam, Robert S., 1996 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - PSA 2000 (Vancouver, CAN) Accepted Contributed Papers, 3.
    Subseries 3. PSA 2000 (Vancouver, CAN) Accepted Contributed Papers contains submission files for the Philosophy of Science biennial meeting held in Vancouver, BC Canada in 2000.
    - 2000 Contributed Papers Front Matter (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Andersen, Hanne, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Ankeny, Rachel, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Arabatzis, Theodore, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Bartham, Paul and Richard Johns, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Bokulich, Peter, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Brewer, William and Lambert, Bruce, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Callendar, Craig and Nick Hugget, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Chen, Xiang, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Cordero, Alberto, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Cunningham, Byron, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Curiel, Erik, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Dickson, Michael, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Dowe, Phil, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Duwell, Armond, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Elga, Adam, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Fehr, Carla, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Fitelson, Branden, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Gannett, Lisa, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Hendry, Robin, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Intemann, Kristen, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Kellert, Stephen H., 2000 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Kieseppa, I.A., 2000 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Liu, Chang, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Lyre, Holger, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Odenbaugh, Jay, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Parsons, Glenn and Patrick McGivern, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Pessoa, Jr., Osvaldo, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Plutynski, Anya, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Psillos, Stathis, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Raftopoulos, Athanassios, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Roberts, John T., 2000 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Rynasiewicz, Robert, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Scerri, Eric, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Sismondo, Sergio and Nicholas Chrisman, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Stanford, P. Kyle, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Steel, Daniel, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Wagner, Carl G., 2000 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Weber, Marcel, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Wilson, Robert A., 2000 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Winsberg, Eric, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Wray, K. Brad, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - PSA 2000 (Vancouver, CAN) Accepted Symposia, 4.
    Subseries 4. PSA 2000 (Vancouver, CAN) Accepted Symposia contains submission files for symposia papers to be presented at the Philosophy of Science biennial meeting held in Vancouver, BC Canada in 2000.
    - Ayded, Murat, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Bechtel, William, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Bishop, Michael, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Bogen, Jim, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Clifton, Rob, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Craver, Carl, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Darden, Lindley, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Dawes, Robyn M., 2000 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Dupre, John, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Earman, John, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Ereshefsky, Marc, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Faust, David and Paul H. Meehl, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Forster, Malcolm R., 2000 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Godfrey-Smith Peter, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Glennan, Stuart, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Hardcastle, Valerie Gray, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Humphreys, Paul, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Kaplan, Jonathan, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Levi, Isaac, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Myrvold, Wayne C. and William L. Harper, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Osherson, Daniel and Eric Martin, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Pitowsky, Itamar, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Richardson, Alan, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Skyrms, Brian, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Sober, Elliot, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Wimsatt, William C., 2000 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Woodward, James, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Worrall, John, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - PSA 2002 (Milwaukee, WI) Accepted Contributed Papers, 5.
    Subseries 5. PSA 2002 (Milwaukee, WI) Accepted Contributed Papers contains submission files for contributed papers to be presented at the Philosophy of Science biennial meeting held in Milwaukee, WI. in 2002.
    - 2002 Contributed Papers Front Matter (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Alexander, J. McKenzie, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Arntenzius, Frank, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Bain, Jonathan, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Barrett, Jaffrey A., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Breuer, Thomas, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Brigandt, Ingo, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Bueno, Otavio, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Chakravartty, Anjan, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Chang, Hasok, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Chen, Xiang, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Darling, Karen Merikangas, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - de Melo-Martin, Inmaculada, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Domski, Mary, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Elgin, Mehmet, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Feest, Uljana, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Forster, Malcolm R. and Alexey Kryukov, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - French, Steven, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Gannett, Lisa, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Garson, Justin, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Glymour, Bruce, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Gordon, Bruce L., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Guala, Francesco, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Harris, Todd, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Hemmo, Meir, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Hoefer, Carl, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Jenkins, Zack, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Kaplan, Jonathan and Massimo Pigliucci, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Kieseppa, I.A., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Knuuttila, Tarja and Arto Voutilainen, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Kutach, Douglas N., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Lewis, Peter J., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Liu, Chuang, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Love, Alan C., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Lyons, Timothy D., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Magnus, P.D., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Mikkelson, Gregory M., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Millstein, Roberta L., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Muntersbjorn, Madeline M., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Myrvold, Wayne C., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - North, Jill, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Odenbaugh, Jay, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Root, Michael, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Ruetsche, Laura, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Rynasiewicz, Robert, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Scarantino, Andrea, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Sesardic, Neven, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Stanford, P. Kyle, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Stump, David J., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Timpson, Christopher J., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Votsis, Ioannis, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - PSA 2002 (Milwaukee, WI) Accepted Symposia, 6.
    Subseries 6. PSA 2002 (Milwaukee, WI) Accepted Symposia contains submission files for symposia papers to be presented at the Philosophy of Science biennial meeting held in Milwaukee, WI. in 2002.
    - 2002 Symposia Front Matter (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Brown, James Robert, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Cartwright, Nancy, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Craver, Carl, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Dowe, Phil, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Dupre, John, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Ereshefsky, Marc, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 2)